/*
   Saturday, December 14, 20242:53:13 PM
   User: 
   Server: JI-RAKIB\SQLEXPRESS
   Database: CrudKayesVai
   Application: 
*/

'Person' table
- Unable to create index 'PK_Person'.  
The CREATE UNIQUE INDEX statement terminated because a duplicate key was found for the object name 'dbo.Person' and the index name 'PK_Person'. The duplicate key value is (78).
Could not create constraint or index. See previous errors.
The statement has been terminated.

